[{"codeQuestion":"1","codeReponse":"1","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"1","codeReponse":"2","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"1","codeReponse":"3","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"1","codeReponse":"4","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"2","codeReponse":"5","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"2","codeReponse":"6","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"2","codeReponse":"7","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"2","codeReponse":"8","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"3","codeReponse":"9","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"3","codeReponse":"10","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"3","codeReponse":"11","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"3","codeReponse":"12","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"4","codeReponse":"13","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"4","codeReponse":"14","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"4","codeReponse":"15","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"4","codeReponse":"16","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"5","codeReponse":"17","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"5","codeReponse":"18","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"5","codeReponse":"19","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"5","codeReponse":"20","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"6","codeReponse":"21","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"6","codeReponse":"22","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"6","codeReponse":"23","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"6","codeReponse":"24","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"7","codeReponse":"25","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"7","codeReponse":"26","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"7","codeReponse":"27","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"7","codeReponse":"28","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"8","codeReponse":"29","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1.- Une fois","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"8","codeReponse":"30","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2.- Au moins 2 fois","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"8","codeReponse":"31","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3.- Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"9","codeReponse":"32","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"9","codeReponse":"33","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"9","codeReponse":"34","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"9","codeReponse":"35","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"10","codeReponse":"36","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"10","codeReponse":"37","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"10","codeReponse":"38","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"10","codeReponse":"39","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"11","codeReponse":"40","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"11","codeReponse":"41","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"11","codeReponse":"42","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"11","codeReponse":"43","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"12","codeReponse":"44","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"12","codeReponse":"45","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"12","codeReponse":"46","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"12","codeReponse":"47","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"13","codeReponse":"48","codeReponseManuel":1,"libelleReponse":"1. Oui","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":2,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"13","codeReponse":"49","codeReponseManuel":2,"libelleReponse":"2. Non","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":0,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"13","codeReponse":"50","codeReponseManuel":3,"libelleReponse":"3. Moyennement","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""},{"codeQuestion":"13","codeReponse":"51","codeReponseManuel":4,"libelleReponse":"4. Hors observation","isCorrect":false,"scoreTotal":-1,"estEnfant":false,"avoirEnfant":false,"codeParent":""}]